Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ nguyhongphuc (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Figma
Adobe XD
Adobe Photoshop

Hong Phuc Nguyen (Aaron)

UI & UX Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I have almost 3 years of experience in UI & UX design. With knowledge accumulated in the process of studying and working, I set a goal for myself to come up with the most intuitive, easiest to use and most convenient designs because I always put the experience and feeling of users first. Besides, in addition to promoting what I have cultivated during the working process, I still do not hesitate and am always willing to absorb and learn new knowledge because I always think that "Diligence in place of intelligence".

Experience

bTaskee UI & UX Designer April 2024 - Present (1 year) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Tititada
UI & UX Designer
May 2023 - March 2024 (11 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

CMC Saigon Technology & Solution (CMC TSSG) 2 years

UI & UX Designer September 2021 - March 2023 (1 year 7 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

C-Suite provides a set of solutions to fully digitize the necessary business processes and operations, ensuring that tasks are handled without interruption. Cloud computing technology allows users to access and manage anytime, anywhere with an internet connection. In addition, a reminder system to prevent errors and work drift and a proactive reporting system to support management leaders and make the most accurate decisions.

UI & UX Designer

April 2021 - August 2021 (5 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

WESET English Center Teaching Assistant March 2019 - April 2019 (2 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

HUFLIT

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Management Information Systems, General · (August 2017 - December 2021)

Youix Design & Technology Education
Certificate, UX Research · (February 2023 - March 2023)